Guide to the Ohio State University, Office of the President (Harold Leroy Enarson) Records, 1940s-2002 RG.3.J
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Processed, 1971-1981; 54.0 Cubic feet; (45) cartons
  - Seminar in Administrative Science Class, 1974 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 66)
  - American Association for Higher Education: Chicago: "What is Left of Campus to Govern: Toward the End of Lamentations", 1974 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 67)
  - Health and Welfare Institute: Cleveland, 1974 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 68)
  - Naples, Florida Alumni Association, 1974 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 69)
  - Unitarian Church Address, 1974 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 70)
  - Continuing Veterinary Education, 1974 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 71)
  - Address to Columbus Bar Association, 1974 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 72)
  - Belmont County Alumni, 1974 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 73)
  - Pacesetters Banquet (Document Missing), 1974 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 74)
  - President's Club, 1974 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 75)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators: Kansas City, Mo.: "Notes on the Smothering of Quarrels with Special Reference to the University World", 1974 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 76)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1974 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 77)
  - Guest Editorial for Academy for Medicine Bulletin: "How Others See Us", 1974 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 78)
  - Testimony Before Special Committee on Education: May 21, 1974 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 79)
  - Open Letter to University Community Re Black Demands: May 29, 1974, 1974 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 80)
  - Sinclair Community College: "The Dialogue of the Deaf", 1974 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 81)
  - Testimony Before the Ohio Civil Service Commission: Jun 20, 1974, 1974 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 82)
  - Solar House Press Briefing, 1974 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 83)
  - Commencement Address By President Ford. (Enarson's Remarks are Missing), 1974 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 84)
  - President's Message for All Faculty and Staff, 1974 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 85)
  - Fairfield County Alumni, 1974 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 86)
  - Journalism Dedication, 1974 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 87)
  - Springfield, Ohio: Kiwanis Club, 1974 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 88)
  - Statement, 1974 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 89)
  - Article for New York Times: "The Limitation of Business Management in Higher Education", 1974 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 90)
  - Misc. Greetings, 1975 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 91)
  - Address to Ohio Dairy Products Association, 1975 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 92)
  - Ohio State Horticultural Society and Ohio Vegetable and Potato Growers (Document Missing), 1975 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 93)
  - History 266: East Asia (Document Missing), 1975 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 94)
  - Ohio Chapter of the Society of American Foresters (Document Missing), 1975 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 95)
  - Chinese Student Association (Document Missing), 1975 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 96)
  - Conference Committee of the Teaching Staff (Document Missing), 1975 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 97)
  - Commonwealth and Commercial Club: Cincinnati, Ohio (Document Missing), 1975 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 98)
  - Testimony Before House Finance Committee: Education Section, 1975 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 99)
  - Newark Rotary, 1975 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 100)
  - "Fragments From the People's Republic of China" Continuing Education, 1975 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 101)
  - Statement to the Board of Trustees, 1975 February 7 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 102)
  - Richland County Alumni Association: "The OSU Mansfield Campus, 1973-1974", 1975 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 103)
  - The Women's City Club of Cleveland (Document Missing), 1975 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 104)
  - Columbus Rotary Club (Document Missing), 1975 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 105)
  - Hiram College Commencement: "Purpose in Diversity", 1975 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 106)
  - Ohio School Boards Association, 1975 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 107)
  - "The Occasional Search for the Public Interest: State Coordination of Post-Secondary Education and the Higher Learning" (A Paper for the Ohio Association of Governing Boards), 1975 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 108)
  - Testimony Before Special Committee of House and Senate, 1975 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 109)
  - President's Club, 1975 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 110)
  - Commencement Talk: University of Detroit, 1975 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 111)
  - Detroit Alumni Association, 1975 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 112)
  - Letter to the Lantern: "Do You Ever Get Bored?": May 2, 1975 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 113)
  - Bethany College Commencement Address, 1975 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 114)
  - Answer to Black Demands, 1975 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 115)
  - Lancaster High School Commencement Address, 1975 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 116)
  - Letter to Faculty and Staff, 1975 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 117)
  - Editorial for Lantern, 1975 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 118)
  - Message to University Faculty and Staff, 1975 June 20 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 119)
  - "The Art of Planning: Fugitive Notes on Thinking Ahead": Society for College and University Planning Conference, 1975 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 120)
  - "Future Financing of Higher Education": CASE National Assembly, 1975 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 121)
  - Statement Delivered to Board of Trustees: "Proposed Initiatives Concerning Expanded Opportunity for Women and Minorities", 1975 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 122)
  - American Agricultural Economics Association Conference, 1975 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 123)
  - Big Ten Alumni Officers Conference, 1975 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 124)
  - National Association of State Budget Officers, New Orleans, 1975 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 125)
  - Moscow, Russia, 1975 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 126)
  - ACE Internship Program, 1975 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 127)
  - Cleveland Rotary Club: "Fragments from the People's Republic of China", 1975 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 128)
  - Welcome to Graduate Students, 1975 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 129)
  - National No-Tillage Forage Symposium, 1975 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 130)
  - Ohio Cooperative Extension Annual Conference, 1975 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 131)
  - Norwegian American Sesquicentennial: Minnesota, 1975 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 1)
  - College Entrance Examination Board Remarks: "The Widening Circle: New Populations and Needs", 1975 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 2)
  - Council of Colleges of Arts and Sciences: Charleston: "The Liberal Arts and the People's Colleges and Choices", 1975 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 3)
  - Lecture Tour of India, 1975 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 4)
  - Statement to Board of Trustees Re Don Scott Field, 1975 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 5)
  - Financial Executives Institute, 1976 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 6)
  - Twenty-fifth Anniversary of The India Republic, 1976 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 7)
  - Journalism Class, 1976 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 8)
  - Columbus Technical Council Annual Awards Banquet, 1976 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 9)
  - Preble County Alumni Association, 1976 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 10)
  - Statement to Board of Trustees, 1976 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 11)
  - Lancaster Rotary, 1976 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 12)
  - ASPA Seminar: "Role of Universities in Providing Technical Assistance to Governments", 1976 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 13)
  - President's Club: "On the Edge of Excellence", 1976 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 14)
  - "Some Neglected Issues on the Agenda of Higher Education": To Higher Education Coordinating Council: St. Louis, 1976 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 15)
  - Friends of The OSU Libraries: "The Quest for Excellence in the OSU Libraries", 1976 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 16)
  - Kit Kat Club: "Some Dimensions of International Education", 1976 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 17)
  - Remarks to Ohio Congressional Delegation: Washington, D.C.: "Restoring the Partnership", 1976 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 18)
  - OSU Commencement: Patrick P. Moynihan, 1976 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 19)
  - University of New Mexico, 1976 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 20)
  - Education for Health Conference: Chicago: "Some Thoughts about the Health Professions and the Universities", 1976 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 21)
  - Greetings to Alumni of College of Medicine (Document Missing), 1976 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 22)
  - Ireland Trip (Document Missing), 1976 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 23)
  - Worthington Women's Club (Document Missing), 1976 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 24)
  - Ohio Foundations Conference, 1976 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 25)
  - Toledo Rotary Club: "Ohio Higher Education--Tell Us What You Want and Will Pay For", 1976 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 26)
  - Dedication Ceremony: University and Independence Halls, 1976 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 27)
  - Address to Rotary and Kiwanis Clubs: Troy, Ohio, 1976 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 28)
  - Ohio Conference for College and University Planning, 1976 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 29)
  - Address to University Senate: "Servants of the Public Interest", 1976 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 30)
  - Governor's Committee on Employment of Handicapped, 1976 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 31)
  - Franklin County Chapter of The Ohio Society of Professional Engineers, 1976 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 32)
  - Statement to Board of Trustees: Dec 15, 1976 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 33)
  - Statement for Publication in Lantern: Jan 10, 1977 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 34)
  - St. Louis Alumni Speech, 1977 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 35)
  - AAUW (Document Missing), 1977 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 36)
  - Mansfield Chamber of Commerce, 1977 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 37)
  - Journalism 632, 1977 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 38)
  - Chicago Alumni Club, 1977 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 39)
  - Graduate Seminar: Public Sector Collective Bargaining, 1977 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 40)
  - Questions and Answers for the Lantern: Feb 18, 1977 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 41)
  - Dade County Alumni Association, 1977 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 42)
  - Sarasota Alumni Club, 1977 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 43)
  - Testimony Before the Education Section of the House Finance Appropriations Committee, 1977 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 44)
  - Western College Association: San Francisco: "The Common Good: Foundation for Partnership", 1977 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 45)
  - American Association of Dental Schools: Las Vegas: "Dental Education's Responsibility and Accountability", 1977 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 46)
  - Trip to Saudi Arabia, 1977 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 47)
  - Pre-Dental Careers Day Luncheon, 1977 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 48)
  - Delaware County Alumni Association (Document Missing), 1977 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 49)
  - The Fifty Club of Cleveland (Document Missing), 1977 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 50)
  - Toledo Alumni Association, 1977 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 51)
  - Sunset Supper, 1977 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 52)
  - Central High School Scholastic Banquet, 1977 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 53)
  - The Importance of the US University in International Development (Document Missing), 1977 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 54)
  - Round Table Conference: Zagreb, Yugolslavia: "Presentation on the Undergraduate Admission Process", 1977 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 55)
  - Testimony before the Commerce and Labor Subcommittee on Collective Bargaining, 1977 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 56)
  - Oslo, Norway Seminar: "Higher Education and the Processions..A Small Essay with Possible Application to the Insurance Industry Profession", 1977 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 57)
  - Editorial for Lantern: "Relax and Enjoy OSU at Its Best": Sep 20, 1977 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 58)
  - Address at University Women's Club (Document Missing), 1977 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 59)
  - Ohio Association for School, College and University Staffing, 1977 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 60)
  - "Reading, Writing, and Mathematics": Ohio PTA, 1977 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 61)
  - Presentation to University Senate: "Retrospect and Prospect Perspective on Change at The Ohio State University": Oct 15, 1977 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 62)
  - Football Appreciation Banquet, 1977 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 63)
  - Ohio Association of Realtors Annual Banquet (Document Missing), 1978 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 64)
  - National Health Council Conference: Lovington, Va (Document Missing), 1978 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 65)
  - Remarks to Southwest District Meeting of CASP: Albuquerque, N.M, 1978 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 66)
  - Taiwan Trip, 1978 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 67)
  - President's Club, 1978 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 68)
  - Commencement at University of Nebraska: "Free Advice to Everybody", 1978 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 69)
  - Report to Board of Trustees, 1978 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 70)
  - Retirement Dinner, 1978 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 71)
  - Miami University Commencement, 1978 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 72)
  - Forward for Theory into Practice: Dec 1978 Issue, 1978 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 73)
  - Columbiana County Alumni, 1978 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 74)
  - Address to University of District of Columbia: Washington D.C.: "An Open Door Is Not Enough: Reflections on the University College Experience at OSU", 1978 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 75)
  - Report to University Senate, 1978 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 76)
  - Phi Kappa Phi Lecture: "The Continuing Quest", 1978 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 77)
  - Rotary Club of Cleveland, 1978 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 78)
  - Ohio Farm Bureau Conference, 1978 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 79)
  - Testimony Before the Education Section of the House Finance Appropriations Committee: Feb 22, 1979 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 80)
  - Curriculum: US Capacities, Developing Countries Needs: Conference on International Education: Washington D.C., 1979 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 81)
  - Address to Miami County Alumni Association, 1979 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 82)
  - Testimony Before Senate Committee on Foreign Relation: Mar 23, 1979 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 83)
  - "The Integrity of the University": To the American Assembly: Harriman, N.Y., 1979 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 84)
  - Statement to Board of Trustees, 1979 March 2 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 85)
  - National Conference on the Impact of Cost Information in Statewide Planning and Budgeting: Arlington, Wa.: "Issues in Statewide Planning and the Appropriation Process: The Uses and Abuses of Cost Information", 1979 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 86)
  - Columbus Kiwanis (Document Missing), 1979 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 87)
  - Orange County Alumni, 1979 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 88)
  - Dale Baker: The Man and His Community, 1979 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 89)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1979 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 90)
  - "Stimulating Creativity and Invention in Higher Education": Battelle Endowment Program, 1979 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 91)
  - Statement on Threat to OSU's Capital Improvements Projects: Oct 5, 1979 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 92)
  - University Senate: "The Changing Faces of The Ohio State University", 1979 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 93)
  - Statement, 1979 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 94)
  - Statement, 1979 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 95)
  - Testimony Before House Subcommittee on Colleges and Universities, 1980 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 96)
  - Statement to University Senate, 1980 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 97)
  - Editorial for the Lantern: "The Oval on a Spring Day", 1980 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 98)
  - Statement to Fiscal Affairs Committee of Board of Trustees: Mar 7, 1980 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 99)
  - Basketball Appreciation Banquet, 1980 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 100)
  - Honors Banquet: Worthington High School (Document Missing), 1980 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 101)
  - "Involvement: Key to the Good Life": Albuqerque, N.M., 1980 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 102)
  - Foreward for Brian Campbell's Book of Cartoons: "Just Another Tuition Tantrum", 1980 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 103)
  - Welcome to University Hospitals Board: May 2, 1980 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 104)
  - Presentation to Southern Regional Education Board: Palm Beach (Florida): "Quality and Accountability: How we are Destroying What We Most Want to Preserve", 1980 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 105)
  - "Black Holes and Silver Linings: A View of Higher Education in Ohio": To Akron Roundtable, 1980 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 106)
  - Remarks to Ohio Public Expenditure Council, 1980 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 107)
  - Address to Sandusky Rotary Club (Document Missing), 1980 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 108)
  - Jesse Owens Weekend, 1980 October 3 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 109)
  - Statement of Nov 10 Concerning Budget Cut, 1980 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 110)
  - Presentation to University Senate: "Price, Quality, and the Bottom Line", 1980 November 15 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 111)
  - Basketball Appreciation Banquet Remarks, 1981 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 112)
  - Columbus Rotary: "The Greatest Single Asset Owned by the People of Ohio- And Guess What it Is", 1981 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 113)
  - Annual Meeting of the American Health Association: Boston, 1981 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 114)
  - "The Columbus Business Community's Stake in the Ohio State University": Statement to Columbus Chamber of Commerce Board of Directors, 1981 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 115)
  - Article Written for National Forum: "Agricultural Research in the Development of Nations", 1981 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 116)
  - Commencement Address at University of New Mexico: "Brief Notes on Optimism by a Confirmed Pessimist", 1981 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 117)
  - University of Akron Commencement Address: "Free to Choose", 1981 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 118)
  - Article for Educational Record of the American Council on Education: "Collegiate Athletics: Views from the Front Office", 1981 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 119)
  - Resignation: Statement to Board of Trustees (Tape), 1981 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 120)
  - Chapter for Bob Atwell's Book on Regulatory Influences, 1981 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 121)
  - Ohio State Commencement Address, 1981 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 122)
  - Commencement Address: Central State University, 1981 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 123)
  - University of Illinois Conference on Administrative Leadership, 1981 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 124)
  - University of Pittsburgh Retreat: "Doing More with Less: University-Wide Priorities", 1981 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 125)
  - China Trip, 1974 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 126)
  - Kiwanis Remarks: Aug 24, 1981, 1981 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 127)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1981 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 128)
  - Statement on Creation of a Federal Dept. of Education: No Date, 1981 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0038, Folder 129)
  - Student Affairs: Council on: Correspondence (Incl Minutes), 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 1)
  - Student Demonstrations, Disruptions and Unrest: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 2)
  - Student Demonstrations, Disruptions and Unrest: Cases, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 3)
  - Student Demonstrations, Disruptions and Unrest: Procedures for Reporting, 1971-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 4)
  - Student Discipline Office: Correspondence (Incl. Memos), 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 5)
  - Student Financial Aid: Aid for Veterans, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 6)
  - Student Financial Aid: Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 7)
  - Student Financial Aid: Application and Selection for Loans, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 8)
  - Student Financial Aid: Collection and Default of Loans, 1971-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 9)
  - Student Financial Aid: Financial Aid Program Compliance, 1979 November 19 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 10)
  - Student Financial Aid: Financial Aid Resources and Implications, 1978 November 3 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 11)
  - Student Financial Aid: Grants and Scholarships, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 12)
  - Student Financial Aid: Institutional Participation in Programs, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 13)
  - Student Financial Aid: Need Analysis Manual, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 14)
  - Student Financial Aid: President's Scholarship Dinner, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 15)
  - Student Financial Aid: Recommendation for Scholarships, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 16)
  - Student Financial Aid: Report of Examination of Programs, 1976 July 1-1978 June 30 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 17)
  - Student Financial Aid: Student Financial Aid in Ohio, 1970-1971 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 18)
  - Student Health Services: Correspondence: Student Housing: See Residence and Dining Halls: Office of, 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 19)
  - Student Matters: Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 20)
  - Student Organizations: Afro-American Materials, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 21)
  - Student Organizations: Community Projects, undated (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 22)
  - Student Organizations: Correspondence, 1972 December-1975 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 23)
  - Student Organizations: Correspondence, 1975 August-1980 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 24)
  - Student Publications: Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 25)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Applicants for Vice-President of Public Affairs, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 26)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Athletic Dept., 1974-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 27)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Black Affairs, 1975-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 28)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Budget Plans, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 29)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Code of Student Rights and Responsibilites: Review, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 30)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Correspondence: Armitage, Richard, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 31)
  - Student Services: Vice-Presiden for: Correspondence: Armitage, Richard:, 1975-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 32)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Correspondence: Enarson, Harold, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 33)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Correspondence: Enarson, Harold, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 34)